<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Course_Learning</string>
    <string name="open_nav">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_nav">Close Navigation Drawer</string>

    <string name="uxdesign">Professional Certificate:---
        What you will learn Follow the design process: empathize with users, define pain points, ideate solutions and
        3 end-to-end projects: a mobile app, a responsive website, and a cross-platform experience.
Category: Figma,Abode
Subtitles: English.
        Course : 1500[INR]
    </string>
    <string name="fullstack">Professional Certificate:---
        What you will learn
Master the most up-to-date practical skills and tools that full stack developers use in their daily roles
        and tools such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, and Bootstrap,including a capstone

Category: Cloud Native,Devops,Html,CSS,Saas,JS,Cloud Computing.
Course : 2000[INR]</string>

    <string name="python">Beginners:-
       learn Python Basics including Data Types, Expressions, Variables, and Data Structures.
        Apply Python programming logic using Branching, Loops, Functions, Objects and Classes.
Access web data using APIs and web scraping from Python in Jupyter Notebooks.
Category: Python Programming / Pandas,Numpy,Steamlit
        Course : 1000[INR]</string>
    <string name="dataanalayst">Beginners:-
Learn key analytical skills (data cleaning, analysis, visualization)
Understand how to clean and organize data for analysis, SQL and R programming
Learn how to visualize and present data findings in dashboards.
Category: R Programming,Tableau,SQL,spreedsheets.
        </string>
    <string name="deeplearning">Specialization :---You will Learn how to
Build and train deep neural networks, identify key architecture parameters, implement vectorized neural networks and deep learning to applications
Train test sets, analyze variance for DL applications, use standard techniques and optimization algorithms.
Category: ANN,Tensorflow,RNN.
        Course : 1500[INR]</string>
    <string name="financeanalayst">Certificate of completion:-
Understand and apply the basic business accounting practices such as the Fundamental Accounting Equation, the Revenue Recognition principle, Accrual Accounting,
Category: ROI analysis/future revenues, manufacturing overhead
Financial modeling/analysis
Course : 500[INR]</string>
    <string name="accounting">Certificate of completion:-
What you will learn
Understand Branch Accounts,Accounting for Consignment,Joint Venture,Investments,Insurance Claims,Average Due DAte,Computer Software
, Banking Companies.,Hospitals,Final Accounts of Sole Proprietors
Course : 650[INR]</string>
    <string name="business">Certificate of completion:-
        What you will learn
        Methods, Techniques and tricks to solve math problems in Ratios
Methods, Techniques and tricks to solve math problems in Proporitons
Methods, Techniques and tricks to solve math problems in Indices
Course : 999[INR]
    </string>
    <string name="financemanagement">Certificate of completion:-
        hat you will learn Understand Capital Structure Decisions, Leverage, Capital Structure Theories
Understand Capital Budgeting Process,Payback,Tresaury Management, Debtors Management, Creditors Management
Understand Various sources of Finance.Course : 650[INR]</string>
    <string name="financetrading">Certificate of completion:-
        NumPy to quickly work with Numerical Data
Use Pandas for Analyze and Visualize Data,
Learn how to use statsmodels for Time Series Analysis
Calculate Financial Statistics, such as Daily Returns, Volatility, etc..
Calculate the Sharpe Ratio.Course : 999[INR]</string>
    <string name="philosopy">what you learn in this Course is to Gain an appreciation of the relation of methods of learning about oneself that do not depend on introspection.
        , philosophy, and neuroscience into the emotions and the unconscious.
Understand the role of affect in decision making.Course:Free</string>
    <string name="artsart">Specialization Course in Art :-What you will learn in this course Model, lead, and advocate technology-enabled innovation and transformation in education and training
Design, develop and learning,
Design, develop.Course:-Free</string>
    <string name="graphicdesign">What you learn in this Course are --Key algorithms / techniques used in the past research.
Category: 3d computer graphics
Category: Algorithms
Category: Robotics
Category: Computer Graphics (CG)
Computer Graphics (CG)
    Course:Free</string>
    <string name="creativethinking">Certificate:-Creative Thinking..What you learn from your Course Understand what creative thinking techniques are problem-solving scenarios or the problem to tackle
Category: Creative Thinking,Problem Solving,Creativity,Brainstorming
    Course:Free</string>
    <string name="leadership">Certificate:-Leadership Principle .Through an understanding of self and situational awareness, identify strategies to perform at your best when it matters most.
Category: character.Personal Identity,goal setting,Mental toughness,Values.. Course:Free
</string>
    <string name="marketing">Certificate:-Measure marketing performance through analytics and present insights
Build e-commerce stores, analyze online performance, and grow customer loyalty
Category: Marketing,E-Commerce,display advertising,Email Marketing,Search Engine Optimization (SEO).
    Course:-500[INR]</string>

    <string name="businessanalyst">Professional Certificate:---Analyze business processes and find solutions to existing business problems.
Category: Proficient English language,Business background,Computer literacy
    Course:-400[INR]</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="healthfitness">Explain the relationship between exercise and protein metabolism
Describe the role of nutritional choices and their impact on health and training
Category: Training,Nutrition,Fitness And Nutrition,Public Health
  Course:-Free  </string>

    <string name="dropdown">Drop Down</string>
    <string name="select">Select Item</string>
</resources>